[{"answer": "Anderson, thank you very much and we are leading on the breaking news tonight.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 2, "question": "Piers?", "qSentId": 1}, {"answer": "Well, I think, Piers, they're going to try to literally hide to try to find some home where the media won't be staking out and trying to follow every move Amanda Knox makes.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "What are the next few days going to hold for them?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "Well, I think that -- well, I know that Amanda liked Meredith and that they were -- they were good friends and that's why they became roommates, that's why they decided to live together and Amanda felt great emotion around what happened to Meredith.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "And, what are y our views as a family friend of Amanda?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "One hundred percent I believe that justice has been done and I'm glad that she never gave up hope because if hope dies then that's the end for someone in prison.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Are you, from a purely legal point of view, satisfied that justice has been done now?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "No, I don't, Piers.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Is it simply a question of Meredith Kercher is British, Amanda Knox is American and it's a kind of geographic thing here where the British feel a greater affinity, perhaps, to the Kercher family and their case?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "I think she emerges with many questions, frankly.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Do you think she emerges with a clean character or with a stain on her character?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "Well, she's served -- it's time served and I think that was the least of her problems.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "Again, on the legal point, when she was found guilty and convicted and sentenced to a three year sentence, not a small period of time by any means, for this defamation, how seriously should we be taking that from a legal point of view?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "Well, we may never know, I'm afraid.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "But does she know?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "How could you possibly get any happier?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, for the most people, the studies show that people are happier on Fridays.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "Why have you selected Friday as a day of great joy and happiness?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "I think people are looking for the weekends, looking forward to it, getting to relax, you know, done with work and, you know, I've also read, Piers, where there's more heart attacks on Monday than any other day.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, to me, faith is all about learning to be happy where you are.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "What about the poor guy who's trapped in a factory job or something or maybe has no job who, just through lack of opportunity and bad circumstance, is unhappy because he can't get out of that?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "You know...", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Do you believe, fundamentally, that money can make people happier?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, it helps, I mean, it helps but, no, I don't -- I've seen people who are very wealthy and they're unhappy, they don't have good relationships, they may even have bad health and ...", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Victoria, you're shaking your head, why?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "I think there's not so many distractions.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "Why can poverty stricken people sometimes find joy in their lives?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "Angry, no.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Or is he always this content happy chap?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Well, I don't really think he flips out but what -- he likes things to be right, you know, and, you know, I've watched him when things aren't right and he chooses to see the best in the situation.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "What gets his goat?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "When's the last time you heard him -- when's the last time you heard him shout, Victoria, come on?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "No, he's never shouted ...", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "You've never heard him shout?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "...and if you -- listen, if you live with me and you don't shout, you're pretty good.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "He's never shouted?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "No, no, that's not my personality.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "Do you never shout at anybody?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "Well, I probably have, you know...", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "Let me just clarify, you've never shouted in your life?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "...I can't remember.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "When was the last time?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "It's like ...", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "What's the look?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know if it would ruin my Friday but I -- like she said, I like things to be right, I like, you know, I like organization.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "So, what -- what frustrates in the noisy, what can ruin your Friday?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "I never have -- I never have.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "Have you ever had a fist fight?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "Well, probably with my brother, yes.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "Not even when you were a kid?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Never actually -- have you ever been punched in the face?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Have you ever been punched in the face?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "You have?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "You know, it's difficult, Piers, but the world we live in is not a perfect world.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "How do you explain that a just God can allow these kind of atrocities to happen, ruining so many lives?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "You know, it really...", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "Has it ever -- did your faith ever get dented?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "You know what, that happens from time to time but, again, I go back to the fact that, you know what, having faith means you're going to have unanswered questions.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "What do you say to people, again, who might come to you and say, I -- I can't continue having this faith because some appalling thing has happened?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "What I say is this, God's got you in the palm of his hand.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "What do you say to them?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Well, no, I've never -- I never have, you know.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "Victoria, have you ever had your faith dented?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Well, you know what, I can't tell God what to do.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "How do you have -- how do you have moments, for example, when something bad has happened, you know, in your life or something that's really affected you badly and you've prayed to God to have that situation end in a happy way and then it hasn't, your prayers haven't been answered, in that circumstance do you not feel slightly let down?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Do you ever watch yourself back on TV?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "I do still edit them.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "ORGAN: Do you?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "Well, my mother has had a great memory and when I started, you know, my dad just spoke extemporaneously and just would go and I couldn't do that.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "How have you developed that?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "You know, it's a complicated issue, Piers.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "What do you think of the whole issue?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Well, I don't -- I don't know that that's -- you know, I -- it's -- it's hard for me.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "A life for a life?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Well, I think the thing is, is we have a justice system and I believe in our system of justice, number one.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "You can't be the man who influences millions of people and sit on the fence about key moral issues like that, key moral stroke ethical issues and you've got to have a view haven't you?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "...well, abortion, I -- I feel stronger about because it -- I feel like...", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "If I asked you about abortion, what would you say?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "...my view is that every baby should live, that, you know, that God's created that life and, so, again, that's what I feel strongly about.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "What's your view?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Well, I think there could be when you say may or may not.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Should there not be a more consistent view?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "Yes, I've always believed, Piers, the scriptures shows that it's a sin, but, you know, I'm not one of those that are out there to bash homosexuals and tell them that they're terrible people and all that.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Is homosexuality a sin, in your eyes?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, it really never changes because mine was -- mine's based out of the scripture.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "What's your view now?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "I mean, like everything else, doesn't it have to move with the times and isn't it down again to people like you to interpret it in a way that evolves when you're known as a very progressive preacher?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Well, you know what, I'm going to respect the law and I'm going to respect gay people like I do now, you know, have plenty of people that come to our church and friends, I would call, that are gay so I'm going to respect that.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "What if Texas eventually, in a moment it's an unlikely place I would imagine to bring this in, but it may change with enough pressure, Texas brings in a law that same-sex marriage is permissible, how would you feel then if it's the law of the land?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "No, it would be against what I believe the scripture teaches and, so, that's where I think the rub comes in with people like myself.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "You could never do that?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "Well, I think if it was that easy, that we would have figured it out by now but it's been overthrown, states go for it and then they overthrow it, so it's very difficult for ...", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "I mean, could you ever imagine attending a gay marriage between two people who come to your church, for example, if they invited you?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "Two gay people who attend your church invite you to their wedding.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "Would I accept one?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "Well, I don't -- you know, if I had time I would.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "You would?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "If they were friends of mine...", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Joel, would you go?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Well, I would not...", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Could you be seen to do -- could you be photographed at such an event?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "...but, I'm -- I'm conservative, you know, that's who I've always been.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "I like to vote on the candidate.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "You would say?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "...good thing I don't have to right now because it's too early in the race.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "...who would it be?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "I think -- are you talking about political issues ...", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "What do you think people most care about?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "They care about their relationships -- their relationships, their finances, and their health.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "When people come to your church, what are -- what's really concerning them?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "Yes, I think they're squabbling too much.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Do you think politicians, today, are doing the right kind of thing or are they too busy scuffling with each other in Washington to understand clearly, as you've just defined it, what the real issues are for people in America?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Well, I think, like most Americans, I would hope that they would work together and, you know, what I -- what I see that's difficult these days is any kind of compromise and, you know, it's hard to get 100 percent of what you want.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "When you see them all ranting and raving and being deliberately obstructive to getting things done, what do you think?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "You know what, I'm comfortable with -- that would not stop me from voting for somebody.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Would you be comfortable with that?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "I don't know a lot about it and here I go again but I don't know a lot...", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Are there aspects to Mormonism which you find offensive?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "...I don't know a lot about it but here -- here's the thing.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "How can you keep saying that?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "I don't know -- I don't...", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "You know what, I don't know enough about their -- their beliefs to -- to point out what they are, to articulate it well but here's what I -- here's what I believe that, you know, Mitt Romney says he believes that Jesus is the Son of God, that he believes Jesus is his savior, that's the -- to me, those are the foundational things, when I look at somebody, could I vote for them, do they believe, you know, in the major things like me.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Well, what are the things about Mormonism which are awkward for you?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Sure, I could vote for a Jewish candidate.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Could you vote for a Jewish candidate?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Well, it's a -- it's a difficult situation.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "What do you make of what's going on with the Palestinians and the Israelis right now?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "We did.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "You've both been out there recently I think, to Israel, right?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "We found it very peaceful.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "How did you find it?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "Well, I don't...", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Does it worry you that so many areas of conflict of the world are religion prompted?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "You know what, I enjoy it.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Do you like being interviewed or do you find it a bit of a minefield?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "Oh, I'd be thrilled, you know, nothing greater than for your children to follow in your legacy.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Would you be happy with that?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "Oh, you know what, I never feel like it like that.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "I mean, are you going to have to keep an extra close eye because you're the Olsteens, everyone be looking to trip them up?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "Oh, well, we -- we have good conversations.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "What's he talking about?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "Well, we like to have a good dinner and we like to either ride our bikes or we like to just hang out and talk or, you know, we may have a few friends over.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "What's your perfect Friday?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "And I respect him even more.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "What's the secret?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "Well, I think he's a man of what he -- of his word, I think he's a man of what his word, he's -- he's always looking for the best in any situation.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Yes, what's the secret of the Joel Olsteen magic, you think?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "Oh, that and more.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "Do you agree with all that Joel?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "Oh, I have some kind people, I don't call them groupies, but people that, you know, they feel like you've helped them and you know what, I -- listen...", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "You -- you can't ignore it, I mean, you must get some groupies, any?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "I don't -- I don't...", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "Do you get all that?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "I don't -- no, not in the work we do.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "Are you like popular like Tom Jones, you know?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Well, I -- you know, it's funny because when I -- when I'm out, even by myself, this is what women say to me, oh, Victoria, I love your husband.", "docId": "111004pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "Ever do that?", "qSentId": 605}]